[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mohamed Morsi"]}, "docId": "130814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "RP", "RB", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "CD", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 31, "question": "What is your take on what is happening here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 32, "answer": "You know, covering this throughout the day, watching the clashes beginning to spread and intensify across the capital, hearing the reports of clashes breaking out elsewhere, angry mobs of supporters of ousted President Mohamed Morsi, even attacking churches, it felt as if one was beginning to see the very edges of Egyptian society fraying.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "And the obvious question, Arwa, I guess, is do you believe that journalists including yourself are coming under deliberate attack here or is it simply being caught up in the general mayhem?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "AMON: It's difficult to judge that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Arwa"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "How bad do you think this is going to get?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "Well, it's really scary and just heartbreaking to see.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "Why are the Americans persisting and pretending otherwise?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "DT", "NNPS", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "Well, it's really an issue of semantics.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "TO", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 157, "question": "What do you make of all this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "Well, I think there's a lot more to this story probably than that's -- we really understand at this point.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "Where is her mother and father to not know that this guy is creepy and she feels creepy about him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "It does seem strange.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "What do you read into all this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "Well, I mean, the same thing that you're saying.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "I believe you've taken some today as you would every day, is that correct?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "Well, you know, here's something -- we haven't had a chance to talk for quite awhile.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Montel"]}, "docId": "130814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "But what is your response to the criticism you've had this week?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "Well, look, a lot of the criticism I think, you know -- first of all, you talk to a guy like Montel and he's been ahead of the curve on this, frankly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sanjay", "Montel"]}, "docId": "130814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 317, "question": "Why are you so opposed to this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 318, "answer": "Well -- well, I oppose medical marijuana -- I want to really start by saying that there is a lot that I do agree with, with both Sanjay and Montel.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CNN"]}, "docId": "130814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", ":", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "So the classification seems to be completely wrong, doesn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "Well, you know, I think that there has been difficulty in studying cannabinoids largely because of a confluence of circumstances that -- that were brought up in the special and in other interviews that we've seen on CNN.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "That can't be right, can it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dr. Levy"]}, "docId": "130814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "Where do you think this is all going to go?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "I think that now that we have more doctors and even Dr. Levy agrees, we need to do the research.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 446, "question": "What did you make of what happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 447, "answer": "Well, you know what, frankly, it was sad, Piers, the story that she told.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "PERSON": ["Kathryn Jackson", "Michael"]}, "docId": "130814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", ":", "CC", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "But in the end, there (ph) was a picture built that helps AEG in the sense of Jackson's clear long-time use of propofol and all these doctors -- not just Conrad Murray queuing up to supply it for him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "EX", ":", "NN", ":", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NNS", ":", "RB", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "TO", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "I think it helped Kathryn Jackson and -- and Michael's children, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["AEG"], "PERSON": ["Jackson", "Conrad Murray"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "If he was just using Conrad Murray as he had many other doctors to give him what he wanted, does that not in a way help AEG's case, too?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "Well, but that's not what I think happened.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["AEG"], "PERSON": ["Conrad Murray"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "So right now, dollar-for-dollar, Tom, your money would be on AEG losing this case?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "RB", ",", "JJ", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "That's what I think.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["AEG"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hannah"]}, "docId": "130814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", ":", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "But what do you think about that, and the -- the fact that she's revealing all this information?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "CC", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "Well, I think what's so shocking about it, if -- if this is, in fact, Hannah who's speaking to the public.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 512, "question": "Right, I mean, Alyona, it does seem a little odd, doesn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "It's -- it's definitely odd but at the same time I think that...", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alyona"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "Alyona, when we look at Bradley Manning and Edward Snowden and all these whistleblowers in various ways, are they heroes to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alyona", "Bradley Manning", "Edward Snowden"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130814pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "Now, finally, one word, hero or villain, Bradley Manning?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", ",", "CD", "NN", ",", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "It's not our job to weigh in on that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bradley Manning"]}}]